拜托
Oh, come on!
喂  你们也要过感恩节
Hey, it's your Thanksgiving too.
不要老看橄榄球  来帮帮忙
You know, instead of watching football, you could help.
我们知道啊
We know.
瑞秋  你要把棉花糖排成同心圆
Hey, Rachel. You wanna put the marshmallows in concentric circles.
不  莫妮卡  是你要把棉花糖排成同心圆
No, Mon. you want to put them in concentric circles.
我要的是这样
I want to do this.
年年如此
Every year.
十码  五码触地得分  巨人队
To the 10, to the 5. Touchdown, Giants!
知道吗  这次
You know, for once,
我倒想坐下来看看橄榄球
I am gonna sit down and try to watch one of these things.
中场休息
Halftime.
谁想出去玩球
Hey, who wants to throw the ball around a little?
来个三对三怎么样
Maybe a little 3-on-3 going?
-一定很好玩  -我可以参加吗
- That would be so much fun! - Can I play too?
我从来没玩过橄榄球
I've never played football, like ever.
太好了  你可以守钱德勒
Great! You can cover Chandler.
不  我不想玩球
No, I don't really want to play.
拜托
Come on man,
你跟珍妮斯分手之后就一直提不起劲
you never wanna do anything since you and Janice broke up.
才不是这样
That's not true.
我想整天穿着浴袍吃巧克力花生
I wanted to wear my bathrobe and eat peanut clusters all day.
我还想在早上喝酒
I want to start drinking in the morning.
别说我没有目标
Don't say that I don't have goals!
钱德勒  你得把她忘了  好吗
Chandler, you have to start getting over her, all right?
如果你来玩球  呼吸新鲜空气
If you play, you get some fresh air,
也许就会忘记珍妮斯
maybe it'll take your mind off Janice.
你不玩  大家都会生你的气
If you don't play, everyone will be mad at you
因为两队人数就不平均了  来吧
because the teams won't be even, come on.
好  我参加
All right, I'll play.
来吧  罗斯
Let's do it! Ross?
-什么  -想玩橄榄球吗
- What? - Wanna play football?
莫妮卡跟我都不能玩橄榄球
Monica and I aren't supposed to play football.
谁说的  你老妈
Says who? Your mom?
是的
Yes.
以前每年感恩节
Every Thanksgiving,
我们都举行触身式橄榄球比赛
we used to have a touch football game...
叫做盖勒杯
called The Geller Bowl.
不不不  你的口气要很骄傲才对
No, no, no. You say that proudly!
反正  罗斯跟我每次都当队长
Anyway, Ross and l were always captains, and...
竞争越来越激烈  有一年  第六届盖勒杯
It got kind of competitive, and one year, Geller Bowl VI...
我不小心打断了罗斯的鼻子
I accidentally broke Ross' nose.
你是故意的
It was so not an accident.
她看到我就快抱住她  就用她的
She saw I was about to tag her, so she threw...
大妈胖手肘撞我的脸
her big fat grandma-arm elbow in my face...
然后拼命往前跑
and just kept running.
因此获得致胜的一次触地得分
To score the winning touchdown, by the way.
你没有赢  那次得分不算
You did not win the game. The touchdown didn't count...
因为你公然犯规
because of the spectacularly illegal,
野蛮地打断我的鼻子
and by the way savage, nose-breaking.
我赢了
I won the game.
是吗  那你怎么没得到盖勒杯
Oh yeah? Then how come you didn't get the Geller Cup?
还真有盖勒杯吗
There was a Geller Cup?
对  这是赢球的奖杯
Yes, there was a trophy you got if you won the game.
但爸爸说我们谁都没赢
But our dad said nobody won that game,
他受够了我们打来打去
and he was sick of our fighting.
所以他把奖杯
So he took the trophy...
丢进了湖里
threw it in the lake.
这个诅咒解除了没有
And was the curse lifted?
反正
Anyway...
妈妈说不准我们再玩橄榄球了
That's when mom said we were not allowed to play football again.
你知道吗  我觉得我们应该去打球
You know what? I think we should play a game.
我是说  都已经过了12年了
I mean, come on. It's been 12 years.
跟你私下说句话好吗
Can I see you for a second?
懦夫
Wuss!
好  我们参加
All right, we're gonna play.
等等  我们怎么过去
Wait a minute. How we gonna get there?
我妈不准我过马路
Because my mom won't let me cross the street.
接着
Here you go.
-开始吧  -等等
- Let's bring it in. - Wait.
亲爱的  把球传给我
Honey, throw it to me, throw it to me!
来
Here you go.
你差点打中我的脸
That almost hit me in the face!
我们要选队长
All right, we have to pick captains.
然后选塔妮尔
And then "Tennille."
我们怎么决定队长
Okay, so how do we decide that?
-装兔宝宝好不好  -什么
- Why don't we just bunny up? - What?
兔兔
Bunny!
看来队长就是罗斯跟我了
Okay, looks like Ross and I are captains.
我先装兔子  所以我先挑  乔伊
Okay, so I bunnied first, which means I get to pick first. Joey.
-谢谢  -莫妮卡
- Thank you. - Monica!
我是你最好的朋友
I'm your best friend.
亲爱的  别担心  会有人选你的
Sweetie, don't worry, you'll get picked.
钱德勒
Chandler.
罗斯
Ross.
菲比
Phoebe.
亲爱的  现在我选你了
Sweetie, now I pick you.
你才没选我  你是没人可选了
You don't pick me. You're stuck with me!
好  这样吧
Okay. All right, so let's see.
比赛场地  从垃圾桶到路灯  好吗
Let's play from the trash can to the light post, right?
双手擒抱带球队员  开始吧
Two-hand touch. We'll kick off.
大家听好了  28分钟后
All right, people, listen. I've got exactly 28 minutes...
我要给火鸡再次涂油
before I have to baste again.
哇  就跟职业球队一样
Wow, just like in the pros.
好  临场会议
Okay, huddle up!
-临场会议  -等等我
- Huddle up over here! - Wait for me! Wait for me!
太棒了  这是我的第一次
Oh, cool! This is my first huddle.
老实说  你们觉得钱德勒怎么样
So what do you guys really think of Chandler?
菲比  你知道自己在做什么吧
Phoebe, you know what you're doing, right?
知道
Yeah.
乔伊接球  我们阻挡
Okay, Joey will catch it. You and I are gonna block.
什么叫"阻挡"
What's "block"?
菲比  我还以为你知道自己在做什么
Pheebe, I thought you said you knew what you were doing.
我以为你是指人生的方向
I thought you meant in life!
开始
Break!
球是珍妮斯  球是珍妮斯
The ball is Janice. The ball is Janice.
该死...
Son of a...!
-拜托  -对不起
- Come on! - I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
这样吧  我们用丢的好了
You know what? We're just gonna throw it.
我来接
I got it!
快...
Go, go, go!
得分  7比0
Score! Seven to nothing!
亲爱的  我得问清楚下
Okay, honey, just so that I'm clear on this.
刚才会议时你说  如果乔伊拿到球
Now you said in the huddle that if Joey caught the ball,
你会拦住他
you'd be the one to stop him.
现在你没拦住  这是橄榄球计策吗
Now, you didn't. So is that like a football strategy?
是啊  一上来就落后是我计划的一部分
Yeah, it was part of my plan to fall instantly behind. So...
来吧   继续
Come on. Let's go.
输家滚蛋
Losers walk.
是吗  输家只会说
Yeah? Losers talk.
其实输家是押韵的
No. No. No. Actually, losers rhyme.
四十三
Forty-three...
我差点就接到了
I almost caught that one!
太好了  我们差点就得分了
Great. Now the score's seven to almost seven.
这次进攻  你右边接球  好吗
Okay on this play, I want you to do a down-and-out to the right okay?
-开始  -等等  那我要干嘛
- Break! - Wait. What am I gonna do?
你
You?
你跑远一点
You go long.
多远
How long?
到你几乎看不见我们为止
Until we start to look very small.
开始
Break!
一秒钟  两秒钟...
One Mississippi two Mississippi...
换防守位置
Switch! Switch! Switch!
不不不
No no no...
谢谢你挡住了我们的球
Hey, thanks for stopping our ball.
-你们在玩美式橄榄球吗  -没错
- You are playing American football? -Yeah.
哇  你好像是外国人
Wow! You're, like, from a whole other country!
我是荷兰人
I'm Dutch.
嗨  我是乔伊
Hi, I'm Joey.
我是玛嘉
I am Margha.
对不起  达琪  最后一个字我没听懂
Sorry, Dutch, I didn't get that last little bit.
乔伊  你是玩球还是...
Joy, you wanna play football or you wanna...
你好  我是钱德勒
Hi, I'm Chandler.
你好  钱德勒
Hello, Chandler.
她叫做达琪  又叫做玛亨
Her name is Dutch and also "Margham."
-玛嘉  -玛赫
- Margha. - Margha.
-玛嘉  -玛哈
- Margha. - Mar-hon.
来吧开始了  第二次进攻(四次进攻机会)
Come on, guys! Let's go! Come on, second down!
喂  是第三次进攻了
Hello? It's third down.
才不是  这是第二次而已
No, it's not. It's second.
哇
Wow.
哇什么
"Wow" what?
我真没想到你现在还来这一套
How it just amazes me that you're still pulling stuff like this.
哪一套  这是第二次进攻
Pulling what? It's second down.
好  是第二次进攻
Okay, it's second down.
你要来几个第二次进攻都可以
Take all the second downs you need.
-我听到了  -我就是说给你听的
- I heard that. - Well, I said it loud.
我可以留下来看吗
It is okay if I stay and watch?
-你只管坐着看  -对啊  留下来吧
- Just sit right there. - Yeah, why don't you stick around?
-很顺利啊  -我想也是
- That went well. - I think so.
我想跟她要电话号码
You know I was thinking about asking her for her number.
谢了  老兄
Thanks, man,
但我觉得我自己开口
but I think it makes a stronger statement
更有说服力一些
if I ask for it myself, you know.
不  我是替我自己要的
No, I was thinking about, you know, for me,
像你说的那样  好帮我忘了珍妮斯
as part of that whole getting-over-Janice thing you are talking about.
对啊
Oh, yeah. That.
好吧  如果这么重要我就让给你吧
All right, if it means that much, I'll let you have her.
谢了
Thanks.
什么  让给我
What? "Let me have her"?
你是说如果你不让  我就没有机会吗
What do you mean, like if you didn't, I wouldn't have a shot?
我不想说得这么明显  不过...
I don't like to say it out loud but...
没错
yeah!
别难过  我们各有优点
Don't feel bad, man. We all have our strengths.
你比较有数学头脑
You're better with numbers and stuff.
数学  你说我数学好
Math? You're giving me math?
好吧  知道吗  算了
All right, look, you know what? Forget about it.
你去追她  我们看谁能追到
You go for the girl. We'll see who gets her.
钱德勒  我要你左边接球
Chandler, I want you to run a post-pattern to the left, okay?
亲爱的
And, sweetie...
我知道  跑远一点
Yeah, I know. Go long.
我就只是
You know, it's like all I'm doing is
跑来跑去而已
running back and forth from the huddle.
你要不要干脆留在场外好了
Well, you wanna just stay out there?
球给我下好吗
Can I see that for a second?
好了  来吧
Okay, let's go.
-我来防守钱德勒  -开球
- I got Chandler! - Hike!
一秒钟  两秒钟  三秒钟
One Mississippi, two Mississippi, three Mississippi.
失球
Fumble!
你是怎么搞的
What the hell's the matter with you?
这是我最喜欢的一件运动衫
This is my favorite jersey.
那你现在有两件了
Well, now you have two.
我的数学还真不赖
Hey, I am good at math!
够了  我本来还想让给你的
All right that's it. You know I was still gonna let you have her.
现在你想都不要想  等着看自己出丑吧
But now, forget about it, prepare to feel very bad about yourself.
我已经准备了一辈子了
Hey, I've been preparing for that my entire life!
我等着看你现出你的劣根性
Or something about you that's mean!
快点  比赛了
Come on, guys. Let's go.
分数拉平  我们没时间了
Tie score. We're running out of time.
42  38  开球
Forty-two, thirty-eight, hike!
我接到了
I got it!
我的胸骨断了
Broken bone!
-菲比  快跑  -菲比  快跑
- Pheebs, run! - Run, Phoebe, run!
触地得分
Touchdown! Touchdown!
铃声响了  不算
Hello, the buzzer buzzed. It doesn't count.
-那是在传球之后  -在传球之前
- After the snap. - Before the snap.
-之后  -之前
- After. - Before.
-这很重要吗  -对
- Does it really matter? - Yes!
但我触地得分了  这是我的第一次
But I made a touchdown. It was my first touchdown.
菲比  太好了  可是不算
Pheebs, that's great. Doesn't count.
-当然算  -赖皮赖皮  不吃会死
- Does so count. - Cheater, cheater, compulsive eater.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
知道吗  没关系
You know what, that's fine.
也许你还没长大  但我已经是大人了
Maybe you haven't grown up, but I have.
好啊
Okay.
踢死你
Dead leg!
好吧  很好
Okay, fine, fine, all right.
你想靠作弊赢球  随便你
You want to win by cheating, go ahead, all right.
菲比  得分照算  你赢了
Phoebe, the touchdown does count. You win.
别吵
No.
我不想再跟你吵  好吗
Listen, I'm not gonna go through this with you again. OK?
这次我要你输得无话可说  不能怪
Just once I wanna beat you when you can't blame it...
鼻梁断掉  或是铃声
on the broken nose or the buzzer
或是你可能单核细胞增多
or the fact that you thought you might be getting mono.
比赛算平手  现在是中场休息
All right, let's just call this tie score and it's halftime.
首先  我不跟作弊的人比赛
Okay, first of all, I don't play with cheaters.
第二  你知道我以前有腺体肿大的毛病
Second of all, you know I had swollen glands!
知道吗  我想你一定会比
You know what? I think you'll play.
真的吗  为什么
Oh, really? Why's that?
因为赢得人可以拿到这个
Because the winner gets this.
盖勒杯
The Geller Cup!
你们看到的也是一个钉在木板上的巨魔娃娃吗
Is everybody else seeing a troll doll nailed to a two-by-four?
好  很好
Okay, good.
你是从哪里弄来的
Okay, where the hell did you get that?
爸妈送你去医院接鼻梁的时候
When mon and dad drove you to the hospital to get your nose fixed...
我游到湖里找出来的
I swam into the lake and fished it out.
奖杯是我的
That cup is mine!
才不是  你想要就得凭本事赢过去
No, it's not. You want it, you're gonna have to win it.
那我们不吃晚饭了吗
Alright, so are we not having dinner at all?
该认真一点了  围过来
Come on, it's time to get serious. Huddle up.
乔伊  专心比赛
Joey, Keep your head in the game.
这很难  他们的临场会议就在达琪旁边
It's hard, you know? His huddle's close to the Dutch girl.
如果我让钱德勒出局
All right, look. If I take Chandler out of the running,
你能够专心吗
will you be able to focus?
你有什么办法
What are you gonna do?
你只要让他接到球就好了
You just make sure he catches the ball.
-其它就交给我吧  -好的
- I'll take care the rest. - Okay.
-来吧  胆小鬼  -开始了
- Come on, you wuss! - Okay, come on.
上  钱德勒
Go, Chandler!
看我的
I got it!
快  这边  快
Come on! This way! Come on!
小心
Look out!
被女生擒抱
Tackled by a girl!
这种画面不多见吧
Bet you don't see that every day, do you?
你这是干嘛
What's with the tackling?
怎么了
What?
我碰他一下  他就倒下来了
I just touched him and he went over.
好  你想玩狠的  我们也可以很野蛮
Okay. You wanna play rough? We can play rough.
准备开打啦
Let's get ready to rumble!
-加油  -挡住她
- Go, go, go! - Get her! Get her!
好过瘾
I love this game!
你从哪里弄来的
Where'd you get that?
我跑得很远
I went really long.
42比21
Forty-two to twenty-one.
就像火鸡  罗斯没戏
Like the turkey, Ross is done!
你赢没什么意外的
There's no surprise that you're winning.
你先挑队员  强的在你那队
Cause you got to pick first, so you got the better team.
你真可悲  为什么你不肯承认我们赢球
You're so pathetic! Why can't you just accept that we're winning...
是因为我比你厉害
because I'm better than you?
真会回嘴  好一声叹息
Oh, what a great argument. Exhaling!
好吧  我要让你心服口服
All right, you know what? I'll prove it to you, okay?
我用乔伊跟你换瑞秋  我还是照赢不误
I'll trade you Joey for Rachel and I'll still win the game.
什么  男生对女生
What? The guys against the girls?
这太荒谬了
See that's ridiculous,
莫妮卡  我只要三次触地得分就追上你了
Monica. Because I'm only down by three touchdowns.
那就得分给我看啊
Then bring it on!
除非你怕会输给几个女生
Unless of course you're afraid you might lose to a bunch of girls.
很好  瑞秋  你跟莫妮卡
Fine. Rachel, you're with Monica.
乔伊  你跟我一队
Joey, you're with me.
你竟然把我交换出去
I can't believe you're trading me.
来吧  瑞秋
Come on Rach, come on.
你也来尝尝赢球的滋味
Let's see what it's like to be on a winning team for a change.
你会让我上场吗
You're gonna let me play?
好了
All right, then!
比赛结束了  我们要去吃饭吗
The game is over? We eat now?
比赛还没结束  我们在交换球员
No...The game's not over. We're switching teams.
钱德勒觉得我对他造成了太大的威胁
Chandler finds me so intimidating that
还是跟他同一队比较好
it's better if we're on the same team.
好  我们比赛吧  走
Okay, let's play. Let's go.
等一下  乔伊
Hold on a second, Joe.
荷兰人是从哪里来的
Where do Dutch people come from?
这个嘛  宾州的达琪来自宾州
Well, the Pennsylvania Dutch come from Pennsylvania.
其他的荷兰人呢
And the other Dutch people?
他们是从荷兰附近来的吧
They come from somewhere near the Netherlands, right?
别想骗我
Nice try.
荷兰是虚构出来的地方
The Netherlands is this make-believe place...
是小飞侠和小仙子的家
where Peter Pan and Tinker Bell come from.
我的天
Oh, my.
别再讲"疯子的地理学"了  我们打球吧
Enough with "geography for the insane." Let's play some ball, guys.
我不跟这家伙一起打球
No... I'm not playing with this guy.
我无所谓
Fine with me.
知道吗  我受够了
Okay, you know what, I've had enough of this.
干脆直接点
Let's just cut to the chase here, okay?
海蒂  你喜欢哪一个
Heidi, which of my boys do you like?
你这是干嘛
What are you doing?
我喜欢哪一个
Which do I like?
对  约会啊
Yeah, for dating,
找乐子  带回你的风车老家
general merriment, taking back to your windmill?
如果一定要现在选
Well, if I had to choose right now...
顺便说下  我觉得很怪
which, by the way, I find really weird...
不过我会选钱德勒
I would have to say Chandler.
等等
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
她显然没听懂问题
She obviously didn't understand the question.
你可以请虎克船长  解释给她听啊
Why don't you have Captain Hook explain it to her?
对不起  乔伊  这是我的真心话
I'm sorry, Joey. That is my truth.
听到没有  这是她的真心话
You hear that? That is her truth,
还说什么"我把她让给你"
Mr. "I'll Let You Have Her"!
我赢了  你输了  我是武林至尊
I win! You suck! I rule all!
给我来个迷你波浪舞
Mini-wave in celebration of me!
我现在考虑要把我的答案改成
I am now thinking I would like to change my answer to
"谁都不选"
"no one."
什么
What?
我现在觉得你既肤浅又
I now find you shallow and...
很蠢
a dork.
再见
Bye-bye.
干得好
Nice going.
你好几个月不必在床上浪费精力了
You just saved yourself a couple months of sex.
知道吗  这无所谓  因为她选的是我
You know what? It doesn't matter, because she picked me.
是我  从现在起  我会跟女人约会
Me! From now on, I get the dates...
而你周六晚上只能在家里
and you have to stay home on Saturday nights
看烹饪节目
watching Ready, Set, Cook!
将你的突破留着告诉心理医生
Save the breakthroughs for therapy okay?
比赛快结束了
The clock is ticking.
我们时间不多  目前还落后给女生
We have no time and we are losing, we are losing to girls.
我们不会输给女生的
We're not gonna lose to girls.
现在比分是42比21
It's 42-21!
差劲  我刚才就是领先那么多分
This sucks! I was just up by that much!
我们还要不要比赛
Are we playing football or what?
快点  你们这些多毛娘娘腔
Come on, you hairy-backed Marys!
我们一定要胜利
We have to do this.
我们这是替全世界的女人而战
We're playing for women everywhere.
想想过去的每个烂约会
Just think about every lousy date you ever had.
每个在亲热的时候
Every guy who kept one eye on the TV
一只眼睛还在电视上的男人
while you were making out.
老天  你也跟装假眼的男人约会过吗
Oh, my God. You dated someone with a glass eye too?
拜托你们  为了全体女性  我们宰了他们
Come on, okay? This is for all womankind. Let's kill them!
对  宰了他们
Yeah! Kill them!
好啊  我也想宰了他们
All right, you know, I want to kill them too.
可他们是男生
But they're boys.
我们怎么打败三个男生
You know, how are we gonna beat three boys?
只剩下一分半钟
Still have a minute and a half left to go
我们还落后两分
and we're down by two points, okay?
落后两分  姐妹们
Two points, ladies.
菲比  你再用后转身进攻法
Phoebe, you do a buttonhook again.
瑞秋  你跑远一点
Rachel, you go long.
不要再叫我跑远一点了
No, come on, don't make me go long.
让我做点事  他们从不防守我
Use me. They never cover me.
亲爱的  这是有原因的
Honey, there's a reason.
我不是跛脚  好吗  我可以发挥作用
I'm not lame, okay? I can do something.
我可以传球  你让我传球嘛
I can throw. Would you let me throw?
这也是我的比赛
Come on this is my game too.
别这样  莫妮卡  让她传球吧
Come on, Mon, let her throw the ball.
瑞秋  你迅速到他们后面
Alright, Rachel, you sweep behind,
我传球给你
I'll pitch it to you.
你传球到前场给菲比
You throw it downfield to Phoebe.
谢谢
Thank you.
比赛开始
Break!
好  来吧
All right, here we go.
32  71  开球
Thirty-two, seventy-one, hike!
一秒钟  两秒钟  三秒钟
One Mississippi, two Mississippi, three Mississippi!
快快
Go, go, go!
接球
Catch it!
对不起  你还好吧
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
不  我不好
No, I'm not okay!
抱歉  他们冲着我来  我不知道该怎么办
Sorry, they were just all coming at me and I didn't know what to do.
比赛还剩下30秒
Thirty seconds left on the timer.
我们就可以把那个呆瓜巨魔带回家了
Okay, so we get to take that stupid troll thing home.
快过来  我们没时间了
Come on! Hurry! We're running out of time.
-临场会议  -好的
- Huddle up! - Okay.
这是最后一次临场会议了
This is our last huddle!
好  菲比  摆脱防守  瑞秋
All right, Phoebe, get open. Rachel...
跑远一点
...go long.
好
Okay.
比赛开始
Break!
我成功了  触地得分  成功了
I did it! Touchdown! We did it!
有趣的是  得分区从路灯柱开始
You know? Funny thing, actually. The end zone starts at that pole.
你还差了五尺  所以
So you're five feet short. So...
我们赢了
we win!
太好了
Yes, yes, yes!
等等  请你们解释一下
Wait, so explain something to me though.
如果没有人抱住瑞秋
If nobody tagged Rachel,
那比赛就还没结束吧
then isn't the play still going?
-让我来  -你休想  放手
- Let me in, let me in! - No way! Let go! Let go!
放手  我是个小女人耶
Let go?! I'm a tiny little woman!
拜托  今天是感恩节
You guys, come on, it's Thanksgiving!
输赢并不重要
It's not important who wins or loses.
重要的是荷兰女孩选了我
The important thing is the Dutch girl picked me!
是我  不是你  荷兰妹子爱钱德勒
Me, not you! Holland loves Chandler!
谢谢  阿姆斯特丹  晚安
Thank you, Amsterdam! Good night!
我们应该多抽空玩橄榄球
We should definitely play football more often.
也许我们可以参加个联盟
Maybe there's a league we could join in or something.
不是有个"国家橄榄球联盟"吗
Isn't there a "National Football League"?
没错  星期天和星期一晚上比赛
Yes, there is. They play on Sundays and Monday nights.
太可惜了  我星期一晚上要上班
Oh, shoot! I work Monday nights.
这菜真好吃
This stuffing is amazing.
要给他们带一些过去吗
Do you think we should bring them some?
他们饿到不行的时候  自然会进来
When they're hungry enough, they'll come in.
-放手  -不  你放手
- Let go! - No, you let go!
不
No!
为什么每次都只剩我们两个抱着球不放
How come it's always us left on the field holding the ball?
不知道  我想是因为其他人不太在乎吧
I don't know. I guess the other people just don't care enough.
开始下雪了
Hey, it's starting to snow.
-把球给我  放手  -快放手  放手
- Give it to me! Let go! - Let it go! Come on, let go!